A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.29 (A2003) FA490
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.29 (A2003)
1919-2004
1990-2003
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA490
125.76 Cubic Feet 96 standard record storage boxes, R3533-R3540, R3540A, R3541-R3557, R3561-R3570, R3572-R3631.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2003.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (digital media) have been separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by Program, with some materials arranged by the RF traditional series numbers.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Scope and Contents
Contains grant administration records.
- AC.2003.007: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-2002; AC.2003.007; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 standard record storage boxes, R3533-R3537.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.007.1; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RF 95054 #38; RF 96057 #47 - EAST BAY INSTITUTE FOR URBAN ARTS - ARTS AND SOCIAL CHANGE APPRENTICESHIP PROGRAM, 1997-1999 (Box R3533)
    - RF 95056 #10; RF 96065 #11 - RF 96065 #11 - PORTLAND STATE UNIVERSITY - THREE VALLEYS PROJECT, 1995-2002 (Box R3533)
    - RF 96040 #47; RF 96058 #108 - ARTS ALIVE INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL (SOUTH AFRICA) - UBUNTU PAN-AFRICAN FESTIVAL AND EXPOSITION OF ARTS AND CULTURE, 1997-2000 (Box R3533)
    - RF 96057 #46 - APPALSHOP - "FORESTRY IN APPALACHIA PROJECT", 1995-2001 (Box R3533)
    - RF 96058 #101 - JUNEBUG PRODUCTIONS, INC. - 1997 ENVIRONMENTAL JUSTICE FESTIVAL, 1993-2000 (Box R3533)
    - RF 96058 #103 - LINKFEST - 1997 ARTS, DRAMA, SEMINAR AND FESTIVAL, 1997-1998 (Box R3533)
    - RF 96058 #104 - URBAN BUSH WOMEN - 1997 PROGRAM ACTIVITIES, 1996-1998 (Box R3533)
    - RF 96058 #105 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS - "NEW WORKS FOR A NEW WORLD" FESTIVAL, 1997-1999 (Box R3533)
    - RF 96058 #106 - ASIAN CULTURAL COUNCIL - ENABLE DELEGATES FROM CAMBODIA TO ATTEND CONFERENCES, 1997-2000 (Box R3533)
    - RF 96065 #15 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA - SAN DIEGO/TIJUANA COMMUNITY LOCAL ISSUES, 1995-1998 (Box R3533)
    - RF 96065 #16 - LA CASA DEL FUTURO - CONSENSUS ACTION PROJECT, 1997-1999 (Box R3533)
    - RF 96065 #18 - MIND SCIENCE FOUNDATION - COMMON ENTERPRISE/SAN ANTONIO, 1995-2000 (Box R3533)
    - RF 96065 #20; RF 94060 #11; RF 96057 #50 - CONSENSUS ORGANIZING INSTITUTE - NEIGHBORHOOD-LEVEL EMPLOYMENT AND TRAINING IN SAN DIEGO, 1996-1998 (Box R3533)
    - RF 96066 - NEW YORK CITY NEIGHBORHOOD ENTREPRENEURS EMPLOYMENT PROJECT, 1994-1998 (Box R3534)
    - RF 96066 - NEW YORK CITY NEIGHBORHOOD ENTREPRENEURS EMPLOYMENT PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1998 (Box R3534)
    - RF 97001 #512 - SWISS FEDERAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (SWITZERLAND) - PROVITAMIN A BIOSYNTHESIS IN RICE ENDOSPERM, 1995-2001 (Box R3534)
    - RF 97001 #522 - INDIAN COUNCIL OF AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR UMESH KUMAR REDDY, 1996-1999 (Box R3535)
    - RF 97001 #545 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - EIGHTH ANNUAL MEETING OF THE INTERNATIONAL PROGRAM ON RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1996-2002 (Box R3535)
    - RF 97001 #545 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - EIGHTH ANNUAL MEETING OF THE INTERNATIONAL PROGRAM ON RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1996-2002 (Box R3535)
    - RF 97001 #555 - TEXAS A, 1996-2000 (Box R3535)
    - RF 97001 #594 - FUDAN UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - RICE RESISTANCE TO BROWN PLANTHOPPER AND BACTERIAL BLIGHT, 1997-2000 (Box R3535)
    - RF 97001 #598 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN - MAGNAPORTHE GRISEA, 1989-1999 (Box R3535)
    - RF 97001 #600 - UNIVERSITY OF COSTA RICA - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR GRISELDA ARIETTA ESPINOZA, 1997-1998 (Box R3535)
    - RF 97001 #601 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR P. NAGARAJAN, 1995-1998 (Box R3535)
    - RF 97001 #604 - SOUTH CHINA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - MOLECULAR MAPPING OF GENES AND FERTILITY IN RICE, 1993-2000 (Box R3535)
    - RF 97002 #129 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - NUTRIENTS, BANANA RESTORATION AND LEGUME INOCULANT IMPROVEMENT, 1997-2000 (Box R3535)
    - RF 97002 #133 - WYE COLLEGE (ENGLAND) - SOILS RESEARCH IN AFRICA, 1997-2000 (Box R3535)
    - RF 97002 #137 - ZIMBABWE - AGRICULTURE (MINISTRY OF) - INSTITUTIONAL REFORM IN NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH SYSTEM, 1994-2000 (Box R3535)
    - RF 97003 #16; RF 96006 #15 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY - SOCIAL SCIENCE UNIT, 1987-1999 (Box R3536, Box R3537)
    - RF 97003 #16; RF 96006 #15 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY - SOCIAL SCIENCE UNIT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1987-1999 (Box R3536, Box R3537)
    - RF 97003 #21 - CHANGA, CHARLES - MAIZE STREAK VIRUS RESEARCH, 1997-1999 (Box R3537)
    - RF 97004 #34 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - GENETIC VARIABILITY IN THE HIGHLAND BANANA IN UGANDA, 1992-1999 (Box R3537)
    - RF 97005 #101 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - EFFICIENCY CONSTRAINTS OF SMALL AGRICULTURAL BUSINESS ENTERPRISES, 1997-1999 (Box R3537)
    - RF 97005 #108 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - DEVELOPMENT OF THE FACULTY OF AGRICULTURE AND FORESTRY PROGRAMS, 1998-1999 (Box R3537)
    - RF 97005 #94 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - INFORMATION ACCESS AND CONNECTIVITY FOR FORUM ON AGRICULTURAL RESOURCE HUSBANDRY, 1997-2001 (Box R3537)
    - RF 97005 #96 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATION AND INFORMATION TO PARTICIPANTS OF FORUM ON AGRICULTURE RESOURCE HUSBANDRY, 1995-2001 (Box R3537)
    - RF 97009 #1 - COMPANIA NACIONAL DE FUERZA Y LUZ (COSTA RICA) - ELECTRIC-BUS TRANSPORTATION, 1997-1999 (Box R3537)
    - RF 97009 #5 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - MARKET FOR EFFICIENT LIGHTING IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1997-1998 (Box R3537)
    - RF 97009 #7 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - MEETING ON POTENTIAL ENVIRONMENTAL BENEFITS OF ELECTRICAL VEHICLE USE, 1997-1998 (Box R3537)
    - RF 97009 #8 - POPULATION AND COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATION (THAILAND) - EFFICIENT AND SUSTAINABLE ENERGY PROJECTS, 1997-1998 (Box R3537)
    - RF 97012 #125 - COLLEGE OF WILLIAM AND MARY - IMPACT OF FAMILY SIZE ON CHILD HEALTH, 1997-1999 (Box R3537)
- AC.2003.021: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1996-2001; AC.2003.021; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3538, R3539, R3540, R3540A.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.021.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 96015 #166; RF 97016 #167 - MATTRESS FACTORY - INSTALLATION PROJECT BY KIKI SMITH, 1996-1998 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97012 #134 - GHANA - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - CAPACITY OF NAVRONGO HEALTH AND RESEARCH CENTRE TO UNDERTAKE SOUTH-SOUTH AND OTHER ACTIVITIES, 1996-1998 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #168 - UNIVERSITY OF SOUTH FLORIDA - EXHIBITION, "CROSS/ING: TIME. SPACE. MOVEMENT", 1996-2000 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #169 - BRONX MUSEUM OF THE ARTS - EXHIBITION, "TOMIE ARAI: DOUBLE HAPPINESS", 1996-2000 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #172 - MCCORD MUSEUM OF CANADIAN HISTORY (CANADA) - EXHIBITION, "BORDER CROSSINGS: BEADWORK TRADITIONS IN IRIQUOIS LIFE", 1995-1999 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #173 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - MIAMI ARTS PROJECT, 1996-1998 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #174 - ASSOCIATION OF VILLAGE COUNCIL PRESIDENTS - CENTRAL YUP'IK INDIGENOUS KNOWLEDGE PROJECT, 1997-1998 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #176 - NEWARK MUSEUM ASSOCIATION - "CROWNING GLORY" EXHIBITION, 1997-1998 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #178 - CORCORAN GALLERY OF ART - EXHIBITION, "RHAPSODIES IN BLACK: ART OF THE HARLEM RENAISSANCE", 1997-2000 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #179 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - ENHANCE SCHOLARSHIP ON LATINO HISTORY/CULTURE, 1996-2001 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #180 - MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - FRANCESC TORRES' "THE REPOSITORY OF ABSENT FLESH", 1997-1998 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #181 - STUDIO MUSEUM IN HARLEM - EXHIBITION, "NORMAN LEWIS: BLACK PAINTINGS, 1944-1977", 1997-2000 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #182 - SOUTH STREET SEAPORT MUSEUM - EXHIBITION "TRANSATLANTIC SLAVERY: AGAINST HUMAN DIGNITY", 1997-2002 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #183 - NORTHWESTERN UNIVERSITY - EXHIBITION ON WORK OF MELVILLE AND FRANCES HERSKOVITS, 1996-1998 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97016 #185 - NEW MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART - 1998 EXHIBITION AND PROGRAM EXPENSES, 1997-1999 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97017 #88 - GUILFORD COUNTY SCHOOLS - TECHNOLOGY TO EXPAND COMER PROGRAM, 1997-2000 (Box R3538)
    - RF 97019 - U.S. INTERNATIONAL POPULATION ASSISTANCE, 1996-1998 (Box R3539)
    - RF 97019 - U.S. INTERNATIONAL POPULATION ASSISTANCE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1996-1998 (Box R3539)
    - RF 97019 #10 - NATIONAL FAMILY PLANNING AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH ASSOCIATION - PUBLIC EDUCATION AND CONSTITUENCY-BUILDING IN U.S., 1996-1999 (Box R3539)
    - RF 97019 #8 - GUTTMACHER INSTITUTE - PUBLIC EDUCATION PROGRAM IN THE U.S., 1996-1998 (Box R3539)
    - RF 97019 #9 - NATIONAL AUDUBON SOCIETY - PUBLIC EDUCATION EFFORTS IN U.S., 1997-2001 (Box R3539)
    - RF 97020 #11 - ASATO, LINDA K. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3539)
    - RF 97020 #12 - BASOMBRIO, ISABELA - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3539)
    - RF 97020 #13 - BRIGHT, RITA M. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3539)
    - RF 97020 #14 - PASCUAL, AMELITA - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1997-2001 (Box R3539)
    - RF 97020 #15 - HAGEMAN, IVAN M. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #16 - HARSHAW, CRAIG, A. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2002 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #17 - HAWKINS, STEVEN W. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #18 - CHUNG-WA HONG - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #19 - IFILL, SHERRILYN A. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #20 - JIMENEZ, MARTHA I. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #21 - JONES, ANTHONY K. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #22 - KATZ, NANCY - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #23 - KELLEY, THOMAS A. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #24 - AHSAN, NILOFER - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #25 - LOPEZ, EMILY - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #26 - MCCORN, LESTER A. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #27 - RAMOS, TARSO L. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #28 - SANDOSHAM, SURITA A. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #29 - SCHMITZ, PAUL H. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #30 - SOOKPRASERT, JAI - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #32 - TIMONER, RACHEL - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #33 - VON LIPSEY, RODERICK - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97020 #34 - DELUGACH, SHARON - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97022 #285 - INTERNEWS NETWORKS - INTERACTIVE VIDEO, "VIS A VIS", 1997-2002 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97023 #307 - DANCE THEATRE ETCETERA - "SAFE HARBOR", 1997-1998 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97023 #308 - FOUNDRY THEATRE - THEATER PIECE, "THE VALLEY OF IAO", 1997-1999 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97023 #309 - GAMELAN PACIFICA - MUSIC-THEATER WORK, "KALI", 1997-1999 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97023 #310 - PLAY HOUSE - "I COULD STOP ON A DIME", 1997-1999 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97023 #311 - EVIDENCE - MUSIC AND DANCE WORK THAT REFLECTS AFRICAN EXPERIENCE, 1997-1999 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97023 #312 - GUTHRIE THEATRE FOUNDATION - "BLACK NO MORE", 1997-1998 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97023 #313 - HOUSE FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - MUSIC-THEATER WORK BASED ON MEREDITH MONK VISIT TO POLAND, 1997-1998 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97023 #314 - JAPANESE AMERICAN CULTURAL AND COMMUNITY CENTER - DANCE WORK, "IN BETWEEN THE HEARTBEAT", 1997-1999 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97023 #315 - KAHILU THEATRE FOUNDATION - HAWAIIAN LEGEND DANCE DRAMA, 1997-2000 (Box R3540)
    - RF 97023 #316 - KRONOS PERFORMING ARTS ASSOCIATION - "AN DUONG VUONG", 1997-1998 (Box R3540A)
- AC.2003.026: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1980-2002; AC.2003.026; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3541-R3543.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.026.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - RF 97026 #8 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - BUILDING AMERICAN DEMOCRACY INITIATIVE, 1996-2002 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #319 - LIVEART1ST - MULTl-MEDIA PRODUCTION, "EVOLUTION PROJECT/AFTER EROS", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97045 #66 - POPULATION COUNCIL - ENHANCE OPERATIONS OF NEW DELHI REGIONAL OFFICE, 1995-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #317 - LA PENA CULTURAL CENTER - MUSICAL SUITE, "SUITE FOR IYA", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #318 - LINES CONTEMPORARY BALLET - NEW BALLET FOR INDIAN TABLA AND SARANGI, 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #320 - LOS ANGELES POVERTY DEPARTMENT - MULTl-DISCIPLINARY PERFORMANCE WORK, "TAKING BACK MY NEIGHBORHOOD", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #322 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - INTERDISCIPLINARY WORK, "A SHADOW OF FORGOTTEN ANCESTORS", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #323 - PAINTED BRIDE ARTS CENTER - NEW WORKS FOR PERCUSSION, 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #324 - PAT GRANEY PERFORMANCE - DANCE-PERFORMANCE WORK, "TATTOO", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #325 - PILOBOLUS - DANCE-THEATER WORK, "TELLING TALES", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #326 - NEW YORK SHAKESPEARE FESTIVAL - "EVERYBODY'S RUBY: STORY OF MURDER IN FLORIDA", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #327 - SAN DIEGO REPERTORY THEATRE - "CULTURE CLASH IN BORDERTOWN", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #328 - ST. ANN CENTER FOR RESTORATION AND THE ARTS - PUPPET THEATER WORKS, 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #329 - DANCE UMBRELLA - "THE ARCHITECTURE OF SEEING", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #330 - BROWN DANCE CO. - "ORFEO", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #331 - TEMPLE UNIVERSITY - "CREPUSCULE", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #332 - URBAN BUSH WOMEN - "HAIR STORIES", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #333 - WASHINGTON PERFORMING ARTS SOCIETY - DANCE-THEATER WORK BY ARTISTS FROM U.S. AND IVORY COAST, 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #334 - WHISPERING VOICE - DANCE-THEATER WORK, "LOVE SONGS", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #336 - ZACCHO SF - INTERDISCIPLINARY WORK, ".INVISIBLE WINGS", 1997-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97023 #338 - WOMEN'S PLAYHOUSE TRUST (ENGLAND) - "MOTHER COURAGE", 1996-2000 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97025 #38 - ALBUQUERQUE PUBLIC SCHOOLS - STUDY OF TEACHER QUALITY IN ITS PUBLIC SCHOOL SYSTEM, 1998-2001 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97027 #2 - NATIONAL ALLIANCE OF BUSINESS - WELFARE RECIPIENTS AND THEIR EMPLOYMENT, 1997 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97042 #1 - ATLANTIC COUNCIL OF THE UNITED STATES - NORTH KOREAN DELEGATION ON POULTRY TECHNOLOGY, 1998-1999 (Box R3541)
    - RF 97055 #113 - SPOLETO FESTIVAL USA - "ECHOES OF AFRICA" DANCE AND MUSIC PROJECT, 1997-1998 (Box R3542)
    - RF 97045 #67 - (ACTION RESEARCH TO IMPROVE REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH SERVICE DELIVERY) - 1998 EAST AFRICA WORKSHOP, 1998-2000 (Box R3542)
    - RF 97045 #67 - (ACTION RESEARCH TO IMPROVE REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH SERVICE DELIVERY) - 1998 EAST AFRICA WORKSHOP - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1998-2000 (Box R3542)
    - RF 97055 #114 - HENSON FOUNDATION - 1998 INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL OF PUPPET THEATER, 1998-2000 (Box R3542)
    - RF 97055 #119 - CULTURAL CO-OPERATION (ENGLAND) - "SACRED VOICES MUSIC VILLAGE", 1997-2000 (Box R3542)
    - RF 97055 #121 - CREATIVE TIME - "ANCHORAGE '98 FESTIVAL", 1998-2000 (Box R3542)
    - RF 97055 #122 - URBAN BUSH WOMEN - AIDS AWARENESS ACTIVITIES, 1998-1999 (Box R3542)
    - RF 97055 #123 - JACOB'S PILLOW DANCE FESTIVAL - ACTIVITIES OF 1998 FESTIVAL SEASON, 1998-2002 (Box R3542)
    - RF 97055 #124 - NATIONAL BLACK ARTS FESTIVAL - 1998 FESTIVAL SEASON, 1997-1998 (Box R3542)
    - RF 97055 #125 - CONNECTICUT COLLEGE - PANEL DISCUSSIONS FOR 1998 INTERNATIONAL DANCE FESTIVAL, 1997-2000 (Box R3542)
- AC.2003.030: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1919-2001 (Bulk: 1979-2001); 1979-2001; AC.2003.030; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 standard record storage boxes, R3544-R3551.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.030.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 97060 - LAWYERS' COMMITTEE FOR CIVIL RIGHTS UNDER LAW - VOTING RIGHTS, 1980-2000 (Box R3543)
    - RF 97061 - JOINT CENTER FOR POLITICAL AND ECONOMIC STUDIES - ECONOMIC POLICY PROGRAM PROJECTS, 1996-1998 (Box R3544)
    - RF 98001 #607 - SALK INSTITUTE (FOR BIOLOGICAL RESEARCH) - RICE RESEARCH, 1983-1999 (Box R3544)
    - RF 98001 #626 - BIOTECHNOLOGY RESEARCH CENTER (VIETNAM) - NATIONAL MEETING ON RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1998 (Box R3544)
    - RF 98001 #637 - UNIVERSITY OF DSCHANG (CAMEROON) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR MARIE-NOELLE NDJIONDJOP, 1995-1998 (Box R3544)
    - RF 98001 #656 - UNITED STATES - AGRICULTURE (DEPT. OF) - NATIONAL RICE GERMPLASM EVALUATION AND ENHANCEMENT CENTER - TRAVEL SUPPORT FOR YING CUNSHAN TO ATTEND INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM, 1997-1999 (Box R3544)
    - RF 98001 #668 - PHILIPPINE RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE TUNGRO DISEASE RESISTANCE, 1995-2000 (Box R3544)
    - RF 98001 #679 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - "SYMPOSIUM ON RICE GENETICS", 1998 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98001 #686 - INDIAN COUNCIL OF AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (INDIA) - WORKSHOP ON GALL MIDGE RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1997-1999 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98001 #690 - INDIAN COUNCIL OF AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH - CELLULAR AND MOLECULAR BIOTECHNOLOGY TO RICE, 1991-1998 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98001 #691 - INSTITUTE OF GENETICS - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - BACTERIAL ARTIFICIAL CHROMOSOME (BAC) CLONING, 1995-1999 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98001 #693 - TEXAS TECH UNIVERSITY - DROUGHT RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1998-1999 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98005 #146 - MALAWI - FINANCE AND ECONOMIC PLANNING (MINISTRY OF) - AGRICULTURAL POLICY ANALYSIS, 1995-2001 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98005 #153 - WOOMER, PAUL - NUTRIENTS, BANANA RESTORATION AND LEGUME INOCULANT IMPROVEMENT IN KENYA AND UGANDA, 1996-2000 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98008 #116 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - PUBLICATION OF ITS GRADUATE PROGRAM, 1996-2001 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98013 #158 - (POLICY RESEARCH AND DIALOGUE) - CASE STUDIES OF DEMOGRAPHIC TRANSITION, 1997-1998 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98013 #189 - ZIMBABWE NATIONAL FAMILY PLANNING COUNCIL - PROVIDING SOUTH-SOUTH SUPPORT TO OTHER COUNTRIES, 1996-1999 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98013 #190 - (POLICY RESEARCH AND DIALOGUE) - CAIRO PLUS 5 REPORT DISCUSSION MEETING, 1998-1999 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98019 #1 - LIBERTY HILL FOUNDATION - COMMUNITY-BASED WELFARE REFORM IN LOS ANGELES COUNTY, 1997-1998 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98019 #2 - CHILDREN NOW - NEW WORK OPPORTUNITIES AND SUPPORT FOR LOW-INCOME WORKERS IN CALIFORNIA, 1997-1998 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98019 #4 - NATIONAL INTERFAITH COMMITTEE FOR WORKER JUSTICE - WORK BY LOCAL RELIGIOUS LABOR COALITIONS IN RF'S JOBS INITIATIVE SITES, 1998-1999 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98019 #5 - BANGLADESH RURAL ADVANCEMENT COMMITTEE - MEETING ON GLOBAL HEALTH EQUITY INITIATIVE, 1998-1999 (Box R3545)
    - RF 98032 #18 - COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT SOCIETY OF AMERICA - CONFERENCE ON SUSTAINABILITY AND COMMUNITY, 1998-2001 (Box R3546)
    - RF 98024 #84 - INDIAN COUNCIL OF MEDICAL RESEARCH - FERTILITY REGULATION, 1979-1999 (Box R3546)
    - RF 98025 #3 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (LOS ANGELES) - "LOCAL NEWS AND PUBLIC OPINION CONCERNING SOCIAL WELFARE", 1997-2001 (Box R3546)
  - Program and Policy, 900-930; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - 900 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - EQUAL OPPORTUNITY, 1959-1979 (Box R3547)
    - 900 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - EQUAL OPPORTUNITY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1959-1979 (Box R3547)
    - 900 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - EQUAL OPPORTUNITY - ADVISORY COMMITTEE, 1979-1982 (Box R3548)
    - 900 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - EQUAL OPPORTUNTITY - AD-HOC TRUSTEE COMMITTEE, 1981-1983 (Box R3548)
    - 909-12 - INSURANCE, PERSONNEL AND MEDICAL CARE, 1919-1959 (Box R3548)
    - 909-13 - PERSONNEL, MEDICAL CARE (INDIA), 1959-1964 (Box R3548)
    - 909-14 - PERSONNEL - IMMUNIZATION, 1940-1968 (Box R3548)
    - 909-18 - PERSONNEL - WOMEN, 1972-1973 (Box R3548)
    - 910 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - SOCIAL SCIENCES, 1960-1985 (Box R3548)
    - 930 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - POPULATION SCIENCES - POPULATION GROWTH AND ENVIRONMENT IN LDC'S (FAILED INITIATIVE), 1986-1989 (Box R3548)
    - 900 - FINANCIAL ADMINISTRATION - BUDGETS, 1980-1992 (Box R3549)
    - 923 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - AGRICULTURE, 1960-1983 (Box R3549)
    - 923 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - AGRICULTURE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1960-1983 (Box R3549)
    - 923 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - AGRICULTURE - WOMEN, 1975-1976 (Box R3549)
    - 900 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - POPULATION AND HEALTH, 1973-1987 (Box R3550)
    - 900 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - POPULATION AND HEALTH - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1973-1987 (Box R3550)
    - 900 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - FINANCIAL ADMINISTRATION - GIFTS (STRAUSS), 1995-1997 (Box R3551)
    - 900 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - FINANCIAL ADMINISTRATION - GIFTS (SHAPIRO), 1962-1991 (Box R3551)
    - 900 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - FINANCIAL ADMINISTRATION - GIFTS (PIEDL), 1996-1997 (Box R3551)
    - 900 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - FINANCIAL ADMINISTRATION - GIFTS (BOYD), 1989-1992 (Box R3551)
    - 900 - PROGRAM AND POLICY - PROGRAM SEMINARS, 1986-1988 (Box R3551)
    - 900E - PROGRAM AND POLICY - FELLOWSHIPS, 1970-1985 (Box R3551)
    - 900E - PROGRAM AND POLICY - FELLOWSHIPS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1970-1985 (Box R3551)
    - 909 - PERSONNEL - INSURANCE - ADVISORS, 1970-1988 (Box R3551)
- AC.2003.039: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2003; AC.2003.039; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, R3552-R3557
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2003.039.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AH 9601 - RIVER ARTS REPERTORY COMPANY - THE CHILDREN OF WAR PROJECT, 1994-2000 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9713 - UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO - SPECIAL ISSUES OF JOURNAL PUBLIC CULTURE, 1996-1998 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9803 - SEVEN LOAVES - DANCE-THEATER WORK, "A PORTION OF TIME", 1996-1998 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9804 - ATLATL - CONFERENCE, "NATIVE ARTS NETWORK: 1998", 1998-1999 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9806 - FUND FOR INDEPENDENT PUBLISHING - BOOK AND TAPES, REMEMBERING SLAVERY, 1997-2001 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9811 - UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS - MEETING, "MAPPING LATINO/LATIN AMERICAN CHICAGO", 1998-1999 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9814 - ART 21 - TELEVISION SERIES, "ART FOR THE TWENTY-FIRST CENTURY", 1998-2002 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9817 - NATIONAL LIBRARY OF CHILE - OBTAIN JOSE MEDINA'S MICROFILM COLLECTION OF COLONIAL LATIN AMERICAN IMPRINTS, 1998-2000 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9819 -INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL EDUCATION - PROJECT, "TOWARDS A GLOBAL CULTURAL COMMUNITY, 1998-2000 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9820 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (SAN DIEGO) - CONFERENCE ON COLLECTIVE IDENTITIES AND PUBLIC SPHERES IN THE AMERICAS, 1998-2000 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9824 - PRINCETON UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE ON WORKS OF TONI MORRISON, 1998-2001 (Box R3552)